<?xml version="1.0"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">myplantplan</string>

    <string name="textSignup">Not on My Plant Plan yet? Sign up</string>

    <string name="textSignin">Already have an Account? Sign In</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>




        <string name="Carrrots">Carrots prefer full sun and relatively cool soil. In a raised bed, neighboring plants will help shade the soil and keep it from getting too hot. Consistent moisture produces the tastiest carrots, so give them about 1" of water per week.</string>


        <string name="Raddish">For the best radishes, plant them in a friable soil when the weather is cool and provide constant moisture. Because the spring varieties, in particular, mature rapidly, you must pull radishes before they pass their prime. Radishes that have been left in the garden too long will be fit only for the compost pile.  </string>


        <string name="orangesmoothie">Tomatoes run on warmth; plant in late spring and early summer except in zone 10, where they are a fall and winter crop.</string>


        <string name="orangevanilla">Squash plants need full sun to produce. Make sure youre planting your seeds or starts in an area with at least 6 hours of sunlight per day.</string>


        <string name="cappcuni">Eggplant loves warmth and grows best in very sunny, well-drained locations. Eggplants grow into tall, angular plants, so they should be spaced 24 to 36 inches apart. Improve planting holes by mixing in 2 inches of compost to help hold moisture and fertilizer in the soil. </string>


        <string name="thaitea">Green beans are all climbers to some extent but they are generally classed as being pole beans, which grow five or six feet, or bush beans which only grow a foot or two.</string>
        <string name="tea">Onions are a cool-season crop and can stand temperatures well below freezing. They may be planted from seeds, from small bulbs called sets, or from transplants.</string>
        <string name="bubbletea">Plant cloves in mid autumn in a sunny location with rich, well drained soil. Set cloves root side down 4 to 6inch apart in rows 1 to 1 and half to 2inch apart, and cover with 1 to 2inches of fine soil. In the North, put down 6inches of mulch for winter protection.</string>
        <string name="match"> Pepper plants should be placed in the soil 18 to 24 inches 46-60 cm. apart. They will enjoy being planted near your tomato plants. </string>



</resources>